J. Grayson Bloskas

Orlando, FL (972) 832-4803 graysonbloskas@gmail.com

WEBSITES, PORTFOLIOS, PROFILES

- https://www.linkedin.com/in/graysonbloskas/
- https://graysonportfolio.netlify.app/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Knowledgeable Web Developer brings superior front- and back-end design to promote organization-specific website presence. Thorough comprehension of complex HTML, CSS and JavaScript programming languages to generate custom webpage design. Through past job experience, brings extensive collaboration skills with all levels of management in an organization, which will allow him to ascertain company expectations and help oversee site creation from initial planning through rollout and support. Detail-oriented approach to maintaining website responsiveness, effectiveness and security.

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- HTML5
- CSS3
- Express.js
- React.is
- JQuery
- Node.is
- Progressive Web Apps
- MongoDB
- MongoDB Atlas

- Sanity.io Studio
- MySQL
- Git
- Tailwind CSS
- Boostrap
- UiKit
- SEO techniques
- Programming
- Web Security

WORK HISTORY

VICE PRESIDENT OF OPERATIONS | 01/2019 to Current Keyzie Lending - McKinney, TX

- Supervised daily operations of a multi-million dollar Investment operation.
- Established clear management goals and devised systems to track results for effective decision making.
- Applied performance data to evaluate and improve operations, target current

- business conditions and forecast needs.
- Applied excellent problem-solving, process development and strategic implementation skills to lead and support all areas of operations.
- Increased company profits through performance optimization strategies and efficiency improvements.
- Managed cross-functional collaboration to drive team engagement and keep members on course to achieve demanding company targets.
- Strategically coordinated operations according to objectives and capabilities, effectively allocating resources to meet demands
- Supported Executive Team in reviewing, identifying and prioritizing strategic initiatives.

MARKETING MANAGER | 06/2018 to Current North Vine Realty - Dallas, TX

- Built brand awareness and generated leads while managing internal and external marketing campaigns and programs.
- Devised and deployed online marketing plans with effective SEO, social media and viral campaign strategies.
- Improved product marketing objectives by constructing communication initiatives and branding strategies to increase client outreach.
- Worked with marketing teams to create, deploy and optimize effective campaigns for Real Estate clients.
- Developed company brand messaging, collateral materials, customer events, promotional strategies, and product commercialization.
- Briefed senior executives on monthly projections, product launches and other marketing plans.

INSURANCE SALES REPRESENTATIVE | 05/2017 to 04/2018 Northwestern Mutual Life Insurance Company - Dallas, TX

- Handled approximately 100 outbound and inbound sales-related calls per week to qualify individuals interested in purchasing insurance coverage.
- Sought out new clients and developed client relationships through networking, direct referrals, lead databases and cold calling.
- Maintained detailed records of customer information and policy sales.
- Connected with prospective clients to set appointments.
- Sold life, long-term care, and other various insurance products to individuals and affinity groups within assigned territory using consultative selling techniques.

EDUCATION

University of Central Florida - Orlando, FL | Full Stack Coding Bootcamp

Web Development, 05/2021

Learned in-demand skills through a market-driven curriculum: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, progressive web apps, agile methodology, computer science, database theory, MongoDB, MySQL, Git, and more.*

Texas A&M University - College Station, TX \mid BBA

Business Management, 05/2018

- Received Jim and LaRue Shanahan Annual Scholarship.
- Coursework in international business, entrepreneurial studies, human resource management, and economics.

AFFILIATIONS

- Young Leaders Network D Magazine
- Phi Eta Sigma Honor Society Texas A&M University
- Financial Management Association Texas A&M University
- Business Law Guild Texas A&M University

CERTIFICATIONS

- Realtor License May 2018 through July 2020
- Licensed Life Insurance Agent May 2017 through May 2019